Ali Afarinifard

Zanjan, Iran

0098-993-149-8394

Linkedin Github aliafarinifard@outlook.com aliafarinifard.liara.run

SUMMARY

I'm a passionate and young Software Engineer packing **more than 3+ years** of hands-on experience as a front end developer. Yet willing to work **Full-Time** or **Remote** with backend technologies as well to expand my current skill set. I'm Looking for a challenging environment where I can prove my ability to solve complex problems and bring value to both the customers and the business.

SKILLS

JavaScript | TypeScript | Next JS | React JS | Redux | HTML | CSS | SASS | Tailwind | MUI | Jest

EXPERIENCE

Asia Startup

Tehran - Iran

Front End Developer

November 2023 - January 2024

- Planned, developed, tested, and maintained responsive websites and web applications.
- Working with TypeScript, Material UI (MUI), Ant Design, TailwindCSS, REST API, React Query.
- Implemented ecommerce Dashboard Panel with React.
- Implemented website with **Next.js**.
- Collaborated effectively with web designer, back-end developers, and UX designers to ensure the seamless design, development testing, and improvement of web products.
- Built **reusable components** to improve development efficiency across multiple projects.

Freelancer

Front End Developer

august 2020 - present

- Developing, optimizing and maintaining the websites and applications with **Next.js**, **React.js**, **Typescript**, **TailwindCSS** to meet my clients needs and goals.
- Presence and interaction with team members to developing websites.
- Collaborated with clients to meet specific project requirements and deliver high-quality products.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Computer Software Engineer - Qazvin Islamic Azad University | Qazvin - Iran | September 2020 - Present